- Danny.
- Hm?
You...
you get points on Mega Rex?
- You tell me.
- Holy shit.
- Is that a Submariner?
- It's a Chrono 43.
Hundred and sixty-one
independent mechanisms.
The guy at the place
told me it doesn't come out
for three months.
I told him. "Ah. this one's already out."
I love this thing. It's so fuckin' heavy.
This is what it's all about. fellas.
Bunch of guys. top of their fields.
ice cold 'saronno.
Face it. men. We are blessed.
- Mm.
- Whoa. whoa.
What are you doing? That's good Chicos.
Just pouring a little out
for the ancient land.
I ain't pouring any out
for the ancient lands.
This is all going right in here.
That's pretty ancient land. Grego!
You motherfucker!
I love you. but you're a twat.
Jeff. you're a little quiet.
Everything alright?
Yeah. yeah. it's just...
Grego's so funny.
It's because he doesn't give a shit.
Neither do I.
This trip is so awesome. Danny.
We all gotta step away from the grind
of our real lives once in a while. right?
Yeah. but this is real life.
You think your real life
is building pretty boxes
to sell junk to people?
Come on. man. this is the real shit.
There's a lot more creativity to my job
than you might realize.
Sure. I guess I touched a nerve.
Uh-oh. Marco's feeling the Earth spin!
- Hi.
Is this the Life of the Party class?
- It is.
- I was wondering
if you know a person that's come in here
named Maggie S something or...
Mm. I don't know a Maggie S.
This woman would have come in here
taking pictures of the students
for an exercise.
No. we don't do photo exercises here.
- At least not on this level.
- Oh. there's levels?
Yeah. so this actually started
as a salesperson's class.
Now. it's mainly people
that are really bad at socializing.
people that work
with their computers a lot.
It's basically a scam.
You move up the levels
but they're all the same.
Oh. so there's other teachers
that teach other classes?
Do you think I could talk to them
to see if they would know a Maggie S?
Yeah. they might. Come on in.
Don't be shy. It's okay. Come on.
Rhonda.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
This is you? This is you. right?
Do you remember taking this picture?
Maggie S or something took it?
- I don't remember.
- No. just-- she was taking pictures.
She brought in cameras and
they took a bunch of pict--
- I don't remember.
- But Maggie S.
What does the "S" stand for?
They do a lot of stuff here.
- Yeah?
- But I'm stuck on level five.
They say I'm too dumb.
Could you help me
to leave level five. please?
They said I'm too dumb.
- You're too dumb?
- I have to get out Level Five.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry to bother you.
- I cannot do it anymore!
- I'm sorry to bother--
- I said I'm sorry to bother you.
- I cannot do it!
Okay. Alright.
- I cannot do this anymore.
- Hey.
Sorry. man. You were here
when they took pictures like this?
A lady...
Hey! Hey!
You know me. How do you know me?
- Fuck you!
Who are you?
Move your hand!
Hey. that's my phone! Damn it!
I'm glad these are here.
I'm starving.
I know.
I didn't have much breakfast.
Does that muffin have
chocolate chips in it?
I'm not sure.
Mm. No. I don't see any.
What the hell are we doing?
What is this supposed to be doing?
I think we have all we need.
We just wanted to see
what your working relationship was like
and what it will be like in the future.
Can I get a napkin?
Yeah. we have them over there.
Wait. I want-- go ahead.
It's okay.
I can just lick it off.
If we're done here.
I'm gonna go back to my office.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I think we can put this to bed.
don't you think?
There doesn't seem
to be anything going on here.
I don't know. Diane.
It'd be unethical for me
to leave the office
without being 100% sure
that this is a safe working environment
for Amanda.
Frankly. for everyone.
These pictures are too blurry.
I can't find this guy from these pictures.
He knew me.
He recognized me instantly.
He knows I'm still looking into this.
I can't have people
coming to my house again.
Alright. yeah. I'll see what I can--
- Hey.
- Brenda wants to see you.
in the Farnham room.
The Farnham room?
Hey. Brenda.
I only have about a-- oh! Jeff.
You remember I told you
Jeff would have some big news
- when he came back?
- I don't think it's big news.
- I just have some thoughts.
- Yeah. awesome. What's up?
Yeah. I would love to hear some thoughts.
Great. So. I looked at your plans.
and I guess I'm feeling like...
we need to open this back up again.
Yeah. sure. Yeah. which part
you're thinking we should open back up?
The whole thing.
I mean. these are just boxes.
What are we trying to
say here with this mall?
Well. I think we're trying
to say this is a beautiful.
smartly designed place where people can go
and shop for the most wonderful things.
Let me show you something.
I was in Sedona last weekend.
Look at it for a second.
Oh. I like the zigzag pattern
on the poncho.
Yeah. maybe we could take
some of those colors and put it in the--
Alright. look. I don't mean this exactly.
I'm just saying
that this stuff is inspiring.
This stuff is cool.
So. he wants. like. a complete redesign?
I don't know. I don't know.
he wants it to be cool.
So. you don't know if it's a redesign?
No. He kept saying Sedona.
but that wasn't it.
- Are the ramps intact?
- I think everything's up for grabs.
What about the open atrium
in the central part of the building?
There really wasn't any specifics
or anything like that.
- Did you ask about the atrium?
- Everything you're saying to me.
I said to him.
and he was frustrated with me.
He just kept saying
he'll know it when he sees it.
- Sees what?
- The new cool thing!
We'll find it. We'll figure it out.
We'll figure it out. everybody.
Come on.
Seth! Your dad's home.
Hey. Dad.
Hi. honey.
Barb.
Who the fuck is that guy?
Richard. You've met him.
He's Tara's friend. He's helping Seth
with some kind of project.
Doing a project at 1:00 in the morning?
- What's the project?
- They're gonna show it
to us when they're done.
Do you want any ziti?
No. I ate at work.
and I'm gonna be eating at work
for the next few days.
because it's a nightmare.
It's fine. it's fine.
- How are you?
- I'm okay.
I'm just waiting on the call.
I thought the call
wasn't coming until Friday.
You know. I wasn't worried about it
until Heather Babies got their call.
Now. I'm worried about it.
- Hey. Dad.
- Hey. bud! What's up?
I saw Toby Harlan today.
And I invited him to my birthday.
Oh. that's awesome.
I haven't seen him in forever.
- Yeah.
- Hey. didn't--
didn't he go to a different school for...
Didn't he grab
his grandma or something?
No.
But he's really excited
to come to the party.
He kept talking about my 13th birthday
when he did the Pee-wee Herman dance
and I jumped up and joined in.
and everybody loved it.
Aw. that's cute he remembers that.
It'll be nice to see him.
- He's really excited.
- You did have a friend
that did something
to their grandma. though.
- Oh. Todd Greys.
- What'd he do?
He trapped her in. like. a bathtub
with a mattress over the top.
Mom. how do I heat this up?
Richard said he wants
to give it another go.
Seth. you gotta go to bed.
You gotta practice tomorrow.
You gotta focus on basketball.
You were sluggish last game.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
Attention. Seth.
We have a fang problem.
Repeat. a fang problem.
Coming right to ya. Big R.
Seth! God damn it!
Now. the door has a little mark on it.
This is our design mood board.
As you can see. we've incorporated
a lot of the bold. earthy colors
from the Sedona pictures you sent.
And then. there's also textures
and materials we're thinking about.
There's sandstone. and then there's
a harsher contrast with nickel plating
- that could be really sweet. we think.
- Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh. So. all of these
are from the internet. these pictures?
Yeah.
- And two books.
- Yeah.
We also thought it'd be
kinda cool to do. like.
a CBGB's awning or something.
What's that. Ron?
The tattered awning of CBGB's.
Like the era that's like nothing matters.
and just. like. cool.
Okay. Ron.
We'll figure out the vibe.
You just keep us under budget.
Alright. we are lightly scratching
the surface. so keep at it.
That's fine. that's fine. that's fine.
Fine.
Hello?
Ron. it's Bruce.
What's this I'm hearing
about a slowdown or a pause
on the foundation?
- No! No. no. no. no. no. they--
- I can't keep the guys here
if there's a stoppage.
No. any change on our end
is gonna be cosmetic.
There is no stoppage. Keep pouring.
Alright. hold on.
I just got an email from Victor.
- Hold on. hold on.
- I can't do this anymore.
I'm fried. I had to miss
a doctor's appointment.
and I really need to go.
I'm worried about something.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I was playing with a magnet
near my stomach. and I felt
something in my stomach move
and push towards the skin.
I think that when I had
my appendix out last fall.
the doctor might have left
a screwdriver in there.
Hey. so this email from Victor says
you're scrapping the food tunnel now?
- No...
- What's going on over there?
No! We're not scrapping the food tunnel!
- Ow!
- Victor doesn't know shit.
- He doesn't do anything around here.
- Ow!
I can't stop thinking
there's metal in my body.
- Hello?
- I'm out front. Come out.
- I can't right now.
- It needs to be now.
I have someone here
who wants to talk to you.
I'll see what I can do in a second.
What's up?
What the hell is he doing here?
He's got something to tell you.
I heard back from my guy.
About the bug we found in your house.
Listen. listen. listen!
It isn't a new bug.
It's just not from around here.
Tell 'em how they got here.
They're from Eastern Europe.
Ron. Hungary.
That's where the chair parts come from.
That's how they're getting here.
From the Tecca chairs!
Bugs are coming in with the chairs?
What the hell are you talking about?
How would that even help?
Other than your house.
my guys only found these bugs
in Delaware City.
We have a contract there
to do the government buildings.
and that's where he's seeing 'em.
The government building is in that city.
and I think that there's
a little connection
- with the government.
- Am I good?
- You're good.
- Yeah.
Mike. I'm sorry.
I can barely follow what
you're telling me right now.
I think there's something to this.
I think we have to go to Delaware.
Even if there was something.
I can't leave work.
- Well. we'll go this weekend.
- I can't. it's Seth's birthday.
Oh. what's he doing for it?
Just having some friends over
and their parents.
having a little barbecue.
Hm. You...
you think he might like a cop car?
- What?
- I know this guy
who has these old cop cars.
You think he'd like one
of those to come by?
I don't think so. no.
I could dress up like a cop and say.
"Shut up. you little jerk. Fuck you."
I'd love to come to it.
It's just mainly Seth's friends.
- And parents.
- I'm sorry. Mike.
It's just a small party. I'm sorry.
I'd love to go to it.
It's alright.
Ron.
I wanted to tell you
that morale is really down.
I know that. Douglas.
I'm going to come in
dressed as a chicken tomorrow.
Don't come in dressed as a chicken.
Fuckin' Mike. What am I doing?
Ron. you have to do something.
You need to walk Jeff off the ledge.
What do you want me to do?
Knock. knock. These are my parents.
Mom. Dad. this is Brenda and Ron.
- Oh.
- Ron.
Come on. I'll show you the kitchen.
Ah.
Thank you for being so kind.
They've been dying to see where I work.
Jeff. Jeff. we need to talk.
Great. Ron.
'Cause I'm getting the feeling from Brenda
that she wants me to drop all of this
and go back to the original plans.
Is that something you agree with?
This isn't working. I keep seeing
the same stuff over and over again.
We need to change the process.
You and I are going to figure this out
together tomorrow.
- The weekend.
- Yeah. I'm sorry. Jeff.
but I have a party tomorrow. I can't.
That's perfect. Party's perfect!
I'm coming.
I don't want it to feel like work anyway.
It's my son's party.
It's like a kid's party.
But some adults too.
Yeah. there's some adults.
Perfect. You won't be so buttoned up.
Maybe that Ron can help crack this.
The Ron who's not such a big dork.
Joking.
Oh. my God. Dude. no.
No.
Hello?
I'm thinking of finally
doing something to you.
What? Who is this?
Sorry. if you're hearing rumblies.
I'm doing this gut reset.
I'm essentially eating
pickles that are alive.
and they are giving me
the most vivid dreams.
Like. I mean. moving pictures in my head.
Things I can't even photograph.
Yeah. it's pretty crazy.
T. I got a much more interesting story.
so just let me know when you're done.
Anything new on the thing?
Actually. there is some new stuff.
Dad. this is crazy.
He must have done all their websites.
The girl at the Life of the Party class
said a lot of computer guys
take the class.
and it's the same color pattern
on each website. on both of 'em?
It's probably the guy
who's swatting me. too.
Well. if he did the website for City Hall.
there'd definitely be a file there.
Yeah. I can't go in there.
This guy recognized me.
If this government
is the center of all of it.
someone else will probably recognize me.
Oh. you could go tomorrow.
No one will notice you. Look!
I mean. no one'll be working there
because it's Sunday.
But the building will be open
because of this fair.
Oh. my God. you're right.
'cause they'd have to keep
the bathrooms open
because they're eating
all that fried shit.
She's in. She's gonna invest.
They're not gonna announce it
'til next week. but she's in!
- Oh. my God!
- God!
- Wow. really!
- That's amazing.
I can't believe it's happening!
I gotta call George because
he's been freaking out.
He's a wreck.
Oh!
Hey! Jeff. thanks for coming.
Sorry. I circled a few times.
I saw the right address.
but I thought it was a barn
because of the barn garage.
I didn't know you lived in a barn house.
Crazy boring neighborhood.
I feel like I'm in The Lego Movie.
Help yourself.
Food and drinks in there.
Excuse me one second.
I'll be right back.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. thanks.
Mike. what are you doing?
- I said I wanted to come.
- I said no.
You said we were family.
We can talk about this later. Mike.
Please. just leave.
Look. I brought a present.
Let me put the present
where the presents go.
Mike. get the fuck outta here.
Let me put the present in the place
- where the presents are going.
- Hey. Ron?
You got any lime?
I brought Tajin. you know. for the rim.
I think there's limes in the kitchen.
I think there's about four of 'em.
Alright. after this. we're doing
Old Fashioneds with Mezcal.
Oh. my God. yes!
Let me have one Old Fashioned.
Mike. get out of here.
Come on. let me have a piece of pizza.
You are not going in there.
But I just wanna walk the present in.
I wanna walk three feet.
I put this down. I have a piece of pizza.
and then I get outta there.
Get the fuck out of here! Go!
Thank you for-- you gotta go right now.
Hey. Dad! Dad. look it. Look it.
- Let's do the dance.
- You gotta do it. Mr. Trosper.
- I don't know. guys.
- Everybody!
Mr. Trosper's gonna do the Pee-wee dance.
Shut the fuck up. Gabby.
Dad. come on. you gotta--
you gotta do the dance.
The what? I'm not doing that.
- Do the dance.
- Not right now.
Dad. just do the dance.
Well. maybe I'll do it a little later.
It's a little dorky.
Dad. come on. let's do the dance.
Seth. I'm not doing it
right now. turn it off.
Play something else.
Maybe we'll do it a little later.
Mm.
Ron. this doesn't feel like what
I was hoping it was going to feel like.
This is kinda like a kid's party.
But I was on the right path.
We'll get the whole team
at the Canton site
bright and early tomorrow morning.
I think I have an idea
to shake off the cobwebs.
Tomorrow? Tomorrow's Sunday. I might--
Oh. what. it's Sunday?
You got church. Ron?
Come on. Sunday Funday.
- Which way do I get outta here?
- It's right there.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to--
Seth.
Okay. okay. Alright. alright.
- Oh. God.
- It's fine.
It's covered. No one needs to look at it.
Oh.
Ron. you said that you would
talk to him about his drinking.
You said. "I will handle it."
Dear Seth. I've been looking
at this Chocolate Kong for a year
and wanted a reason to buy it.
I don't know you very well.
but if you're anything like your dad.
I know you're a good person.
Happy birthday. a friend.
Alright. everybody.
Spread out.
Feel the space.
We're gonna be here all day.
so feel free to question everything.
even things that we are
far down the road on.
Alright? Go. team.
- It's fucking hot. Ron.
- I know. Louis.
What am I supposed to do?
What the hell is that?
Easy. Easy. Robbie. You got this. Robbie.
- You got it. You got it. Robbie.
- Hey!
- You got it. You got it.
What the fuck are you doing?
You can't trespass.
Relax. relax. alright?
Robbie lives down the road.
Just let us finish. We'll be outta here.
- Finish what?
- The crawler course.
Robbie's trying
to precision guide his truck
over the course slowly without it falling.
- Are you kidding me?
- Hey. it's the farthest I got
- without falling off.
- Hey. concentrate.
Don't worry about this loser.
Hey. get your fucking toys
- and get the fuck off the property!
- Ron? Ron. calm down.
- Shut up!
- Get the fuck away from...
I think I'm ready
to do something to you now.
Good. then come get me then. fucker!
- Come and fucking get me!
- You gotta calm down.
Hey!
What the fuck?
What the fuck am I looking for here?
What am I looking for?
Sir?
What are you doing in here?
- What?
- What are you doing in here?
I'm Debbie's brother.
Debbie? Debbie Rafferty?
Yeah.
Come here. I'll show you.
Yeah. come here.
Yeah. this isn't a problem. I'll show you.
- You'll show me?
- Yeah.
Get the fuck back here!
Hey!
Who are you? Come here. you!
Fuck!